<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
  <LocalizedText>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_HSD_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Historical Spawn Dates Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_HSD_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Simulate history in this game mode with four timelines to choose from, including era or year based timelines and start date customisation from the setup menu. Civilizations and city-states will not appear on the map until their start date. Compatible with all civilization and unit mods, and all map types.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Autoplay is enabled for human players until the start date. New players receive units and bonuses based on the progress of other players and the current era when they start the game. Isolated and Colonial civilizations have special starting conditions and bonuses. Revolts will surround the starting plot, converting cities and causing invasions nearby. Gameplay effects and mod settings can be changed from the setup menu.[NEWLINE]</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_HSD_TIMELINE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Timelines</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_HSD_TIMELINE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Choose a timeline from the setup menu:[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Standard: Based on culture[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]True Start: Based on founding date in Civilopedia[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Leader Start: Based on leader date[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Era Timeline: Based on starting era[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Era Start Mode: Converts any year-based timeline into era start[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Lite Mode: Only Isolated and Colonial civilizations receive start dates from the selected timeline[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Input Start Dates: Edit the selected timeline from the setup menu</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_COLONIZATION_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonization Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_COLONIZATION_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>European civilizations will spawn colonies on foreign continents after discovering Cartography and advancing into every new era until the Modern Era. Colonies start with military units, workers and a Harbor. Colonies will spawn on different continents depending on the player, and will select the best plot location based on historical conditions. Includes option to create colonies for AI players only.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]For Earth maps. Detects the following continents: Africa, Asia, Australia, North America, South America, Oceania, Siberia, Zealandia[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_RAGING_BARBARIANS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Raging Barbarians Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_GAMEMODE_RAGING_BARBARIANS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Barbarian camps have historical names and spawn unique units based on the continent and game era. These units are weaker versions of civilization unique units and can be viewed from the Civilopedia. Tribe name visible on unit tooltip.[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]For Earth maps. Detects the following continents: Africa, Asia, Australia, Europe, Greenlandia, Madagascaria, North America, South America, Oceania, Siberia, Zealandia[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Disabled with Barbarian Clans.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet][COLOR_Civ6Red]Requires all DLC and Expansions![NEWLINE]</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_INVASIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Barbarian Invasions</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_INVASIONS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Barbarians will invade all major players at the end of the Ancient, Classical and Medieval Eras, starting when the era countdown begins. Players receive an invasion event popup message. Invasions for Europe and Asia have historical names based on location. The number of invasion units scales with difficulty and era. Invasions will spawn from a nearby unoccupied plot on the same continent.[NEWLINE]</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_ADVANCED_OPTIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Show Advanced Options</Text>
    </Replace>
 	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_ADVANCED_OPTIONS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Not required to configure. The default choices are the recommended settings.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HISTORICAL_SPAWN_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Activate Historical Spawn Dates or Eras</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HISTORICAL_SPAWN_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Disable to turn off all HSD features and gameplay changes.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Use this option to disable the mod without changing your active mods.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HISTORICAL_SPAWN_ERA_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Era Start Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HISTORICAL_SPAWN_ERA_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Players will appear at the beginning of a new Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Compatible with all timelines[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Compatible with start dates input from the setup menu[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Start dates are based on the timeline option[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Converts the year into era automatically[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Start dates not displayed in-game with this option (except when Era Timeline is selected)</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_BALANCE_HSD" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Balance system activated</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_BALANCE_HSD_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[COLOR_Civ6Red]Disabling this option is not recommended.[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Disable to turn off all starting bonuses and spawn zones for new players.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_BOOST" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Complete Boosted Techs and Civics</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_BOOST_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Eureka boosts that are recieved on spawn will complete a technology or civic instead.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]New civilizations will be more advanced with this option enabled.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_GRANT_GPP" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Bonus Great Person Points</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_GRANT_GPP_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Receive a burst of Great Person points towards all Great People when spawning (adjusted for Game Speed)</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_UNIQUE_UNITS" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Spawn Unique Units</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_UNIQUE_UNITS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Unique units will be included in the starting units</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_ERA_BUILDING" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Era Buildings for all Civs</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_ERA_BUILDING_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>All Civs with HSD receive an Era Building in every city which boosts yields[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]By default when this option is disabled, only Colonial Civs will receive Era Buildings.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COLONIZATION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonization Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COLONIZATION_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Activate dynamic colony generation for western European civilizations. Colonies will spawn at the beginning of every game era starting with the Renaissance. Colonies will spawn on different continents depending on the player, and will select the best plot location based on scripted conditions. Cartography must be researched at the time of the era transition to spawn colonies. If a player researches Cartography after an era transition, the colonies that were meant to spawn that era will spawn during the next era transition. This effect is cumulative, so multiple eras worth of colonies can be spawned if there is available land.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Custom civilizations can be added to this list in the mod files.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COLONIZATION_PLAYER" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Spawn player colonies</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COLONIZATION_PLAYER_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonization Mode will include the human player.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]If this option is disabled, only AI players will receive colonies.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_FLIP_ZONES" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Disable Free City revolts</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_FLIP_ZONES_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Cities in the Spawn Zone will not revolt. New players can still Declare War if the Spawn Zone is occupied.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_RANGE" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Dynamic Spawn Zones</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_RANGE_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>If a spawn zone is occupied and a new starting plot is chosen, cities will revolt around the new starting plot instead of the original spawn zone.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_Civ6Red]Not recommended for Earth maps.[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_AGE" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Golden Age Start</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_AGE_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>+1 Era Score per turn is earned from the start of the game for players waiting to spawn. This will generate an excessive amount of Era Score and guarantee a Golden Age for any player spawning after the Ancient Era.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]By default when this option is disabled, Era Score is not earned until the first Civilization enters the Classical Era (measured by tech or civic progress). Depending on when this happens, there may not be enough Era Score to prevent a Dark Age during the first era transition for all players waiting to spawn.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LESSER_ERA" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Lesser Era Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LESSER_ERA_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Starting units for new players will be one era behind the current Game Era. Compatible with dynamic and static unit spawn options.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LITE_MODE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Lite Mode</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LITE_MODE_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Isolated and Colonial players or city-states will receive start dates. All others start on turn 1 like a normal game. Starting dates for Isolated and Colonial players are based on the selected timeline option[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Compatible with all timelines[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Compatible with Era mode[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Start dates not displayed in-game with this option</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_CONVERT_CITIES" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Convert Cities</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_CONVERT_CITIES_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Cities in the spawn zone for a new player will be directly converted to that player. Always converts the capital if the starting plot is owned by another player. Surrounding cities are converted under the following conditions:[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Not an original capital[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Not the owner's last city[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]No established Governor in city[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When this option is disabled, cities in the spawn zone will convert to the Free Cities faction according to the same conditions</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_CONVERT_SPAWN_ZONES" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Spawn Zone Type</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_CONVERT_SPAWN_ZONES_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Choose a type of spawn zone. This will determine which cities are included in the spawn zone. Use the Convert Cities option above to change what happens to cities in the spawn zone.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_CLASSIC_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Classic</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_CLASSIC_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Try to convert one city per player within the spawn zone (excluding the capital). The entire spawn zone is scanned for possible cities, and obstacles are ignored.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_ITERATIVE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Iterative</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_ITERATIVE_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Try to convert every city within the spawn zone that is not separated by mountains or water. The city plot must have a reachable path entirely within the spawn zone to be converted.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_ALL_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>All Cities</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_SPAWNZONE_ALL_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Try to convert every city within the spawn zone. Obstacles are ignored.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LOYAL_HARBORS" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Loyal Harbors</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_LOYAL_HARBORS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Coastal cities on foreign continents with a Harbor that is not pillaged will always remain loyal to the owner. Colonies start with a Harbor.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COMANDANTES_INDUSTRIAL_ERA" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Industrial Era Comandantes</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COMANDANTES_INDUSTRIAL_ERA_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Gran Colombia Comandante unique units will spawn in the Industrial Era (all previous Era units will spawn at once)</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COMANDANTES_SLIDER" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Comandante Starting Era</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_COMANDANTES_SLIDER_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Starting era for Gran Colombia's Comandante General to appear. This option should match their start date.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]1 = Classical (default)[NEWLINE]2 = Medieval[NEWLINE]3 = Renaissance[NEWLINE]4 = Industrial[NEWLINE]5 = Modern[NEWLINE]6 = Atomic[NEWLINE]7 = Information[NEWLINE]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<!-- Spawn Date Tables -->
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_INPUT_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_List] Input Start Dates Manually</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_INPUT_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Edit start dates from the selected timeline. Dates must be entered in number format. Use negative numbers for BC and positive for AD. This will override all other dates visible in the setup menu or timeline files. Start dates visible under player items in the setup menu will not reflect the dates entered here.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Use this option to enter start dates for modded civilizations or leaders that are missing from the timeline[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]When the Era Start timeline is selected, enter starting dates as single digits representing the index of the era: 0, 1, 2, ... where 0 = Ancient, 1 = Classical, 2 = Medieval, ...[NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Start dates not displayed in-game with this option</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_DATE_TABLES_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Timeline</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_STANDARD_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Standard</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_STANDARD_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Based on a mixture of historical realism and gameplay balance</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_TRUE_START_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>True Historical Starts</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_TRUE_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Based on the national founding dates for countries</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_LEADER_START_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Leader Start</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_LEADER_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Based on the birth date of the Leader.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_ERA_START_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Era Start</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_ERA_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Start dates are defined by era.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<!-- Other Options -->
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_RANGE_SLIDER" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Spawn Range</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SPAWN_RANGE_SLIDER_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Set the range surrounding the starting plot to be searched for a suitable location for a new city, if the spawn zone is occupied.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]If a new city cannot be built within this range, the new player will spawn on the nearest unoccupied plot to the starting plot.</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_RAGING_BARBARIANS" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Raging Barbarians Mode</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_RAGING_BARBARIANS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Geographically dependant barbarian camps with unique units linked to the continent.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_Civ6Red]Requires all DLC and Expansions![ENDCOLOR]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_PEACEFUL_SPAWN" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Peaceful Spawns</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_PEACEFUL_SPAWN_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Activate the PeacefulSpawns list. Players in this list will not declare war when spawning.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Define the players in this list from the file IsolatedCivs.sql</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_RESTRICT_SPAWN" Language="en_US">
      <Text>One-City Spawns</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_RESTRICT_SPAWN_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Activate the RestrictedSpawns list. Players in this list will only try to convert their capital city when spawning.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Define the players in this list from the file IsolatedCivs.sql</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_UNIQUE_SPAWN" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Unique Spawn Zones</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_UNIQUE_SPAWN_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Activate the UniqueSpawnZones list. Players in this list will use scripted spawn zone conditions.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_Bullet]Define the players in this list from the file IsolatedCivs.sql. Define the conditions for a unique spawn zone in ScriptHSD.lua in function GetUniqueSpawnZone()</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_IGNORE_GOVERNOR" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Convert Cities with Governor</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_IGNORE_GOVERNOR_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Cities with established governors can be converted in the spawn zone. When this option is disabled, cities with an established governor will not be converted.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_OVERRIDE_SPAWN" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Convert Any City</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_OVERRIDE_SPAWN_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Any city can be converted in a spawn zone, including capitals, city-states and a player's final city. Use at your own risk!</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_UNIT_SPAWN_TYPES_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Unit Lists</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_UNIT_SPAWN_TYPES_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Choose from dynamically spawning units or a predefined list.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_DYNAMIC_UNITS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Dynamic</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_DYNAMIC_UNITS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Starting units are based on tech or civic progress and enabled mods. This option supports any mod that adds units, and unique units are always available.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_STATIC_UNITS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Static</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_STATIC_UNITS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Starting units are based on a predefined list for each player and the current era. Choose between generic units or unique units. If a unit on the list does not exist in the current game (due to mod changes) then it will spawn dyamically.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Historical Spawn Date</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_ERASTART_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Starting Era</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_ISOLATED_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Isolated Civilization</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_ISOLATED_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Start the game without any bonus technology or civics. [ICON_TradeRoute]Trade Routes to more advanced civilizations grant +1 [ICON_Science]Science for every technology that civilization is ahead of them, and +1 [ICON_Culture]Culture for every civic.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_COLONIAL_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonial Civilization</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_COLONIAL_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Start the game with the Democracy government unlocked. Receive the Era Building in all cities. [ICON_TradeRoute]Trade Routes to more advanced civilizations grant +1 [ICON_Science]Science for every three technologies that civilization is ahead of them, and +1 [ICON_Culture]Culture for every three civics.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_COLONIZING_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonizing Civilization</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_COLONIZING_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>This civilization can spawn colonies on foreign continents after discovering Cartography and advancing into a new era, starting from the Renaissance era until the Modern Era.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_RESTRICTED_PLAYER_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>One-City Spawn</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_RESTRICTED_PLAYER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>This civilization will spawn with only one city in their spawn zone.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_PEACEFUL_PLAYER_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Pacifist Civilization</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_PEACEFUL_PLAYER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>This civilization will not declare war when it converts a city in a spawn zone.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_UNIQUE_SPAWN_PLAYER_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Unique Spawn Zone</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_UNIQUE_SPAWN_PLAYER_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>This civilization has a unique spawn zone.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_RENAME_CAPITALS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Rename Capitals</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_RENAME_CAPITALS_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Cities which are converted into capital cities for new players will always use the capital name for that player. The original name for the converted city will be replaced.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When this option is disabled, converted cities will keep the name given by the previous owner or from real city name mods.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_CONVERT_MODE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Convert as New City</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_CONVERT_MODE_DESCRIPTION" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Destroy and recreate cities upon conversion. The new player will be marked as the original owner of all cities they convert, including their capital.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When this option is disabled, cities are converted using the default game method that conquers the city, inflicting damage and marking the city as originally owned by another player. This can cause new players to not have an original capital. This does not prevent Domination victory.</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_INVASION_DIFFICULTY_SLIDER_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Invasion Difficulty</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_INVASION_DIFFICULTY_SLIDER_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>1 = Easy: Barbarian units always spawn the minimum amount[NEWLINE]2 = Normal: Barbarians receive bonus units based on the era count[NEWLINE]3 = Hard: Barbarian receive bonus units based on the era count and the game difficulty setting (starting at 1 unit on Settler, increasing with difficulty by 1 unit every 2 levels)</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SETTLER_BONUS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Settler Bonus</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_SETTLER_BONUS_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Choose an option for the number of bonus settlers</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_ERA_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Era Count</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_ERA_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Number of settlers increases linearly with era count</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_CITY_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Average City Count</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_CITY_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Number of settlers is based on the average number of cities owned by other players</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_NONE_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>None</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_HSD_SETTLER_BONUS_NONE_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>No bonus settlers</Text>
    </Replace>
	<!-- Headers and Footers -->
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_MAIN_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bolt] [COLOR_Civ6Yellow]Historical Spawn Dates[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_Bolt] </Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_FOOTER_MAIN_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bolt] [COLOR_Civ6Yellow]Historical Spawn Dates[ENDCOLOR] [ICON_Bolt]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_BASE_OPTIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bullet] Core Features [ICON_Bullet]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_SPAWN_OPTIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bullet] Spawn Zones [ICON_Bullet]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_TIMELINE_OPTIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bullet] Timelines [ICON_Bullet]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_BOOST_OPTIONS_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bullet] Bonuses [ICON_Bullet]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_HSD_HEADER_GAME_MODES_NAME" Language="en_US">
      <Text>[ICON_Bullet] Game Modes [ICON_Bullet]</Text>
    </Replace>
	<!-- Legacy Support for old saves -->
	<Replace Tag="LOC_MAP_OLD_WORLD_START" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Spawn Dates</Text>
    </Replace>	
	<Replace Tag="LOC_OLD_WORLD_START" Language="en_US">
      <Text>All Civs</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_OLD_WORLD_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>All Civilizations use Historical Spawn Dates</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_NEW_WORLD_START" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Colonial + Isolated Civs</Text>
    </Replace>
	<Replace Tag="LOC_NEW_WORLD_START_DESC" Language="en_US">
      <Text>Only Colonial and Isolated Civs use Historical Spawn Dates</Text>
    </Replace>	
  </LocalizedText>
</GameData>
